all right so we're in week n of trying
to make history we've been trying to
turn $100 into a million in 60 days but
the 60 days have already passed but for
me personally that's okay because we're
still up on the challenge and we're very
close to the goal so we're going to keep
it going until we complete the challenge
all trades are being shown here on
YouTube My telegram Discord everywhere
so you guys can follow along and learn
from my trades we started 8 weeks ago
where I took my first attempt to the
challenge and then we blew the account
but then I got right back in and we
started once again where we're here now
on week 9 and it's honestly been crazy
Journey but I'm ready for it we're we
tooken the $100 all the way up to
$130,000 but now we're going to try and
take these $130,000 into
$260,000 so let's let the series
begin all right so you know it's serious
day one bringing the pressure you know
I'm bringing the heat cuz I got the heat
turtleneck or whatever this is no but
for real last week we didn't hit our
goal of 160 for the week we're at 1 30
look let me show you guys this is where
we currently are on the account 130,000
this is the second time in this
challenge that we didn't hit our goal
for the week but this
week I'm bringing the heat let me show
you guys all right so obviously last
week we had AUD CAD that we were looking
for the Sals up here we caught them
everything went great and then this is
where we pretty much capped our profits
we tried to enter another trade but then
this trade right here hit us out of
break even lost a trade and now this
trade has been accumulating at this zone
right here for about 8 days and this is
where a lot of Traders think that this
Market is consolidating but it's not
this Market is just building up cuz it's
about to pop either to the upside or
it's about to pop to the downside but we
know it's going to pop to the downside
or I'm sorry we have a high probability
it might pop to the downside because we
have the weekly time frame bearish the
daily time frame bearish and the 4H hour
time frame bearish we have three time
frames that are going to the downside so
this accumulation that's doing here we
have a higher probability of it popping
down versus to the upside and that's why
I'm going to no longer take a trade
within this Zone as I was doing before
which I've been very fortunate to make
great profits then I'm going to be
waiting for this price to break this
Zone and retest it clearly it's a very
well level respected of support very
well respected level of resistance and
now this is what I'm going to be wait in
order to take this trade next we have
nzdjpy so this is a trade that I've been
analyzing for 2 weeks now and it's
giving us very clear indications now
very similar to AUD CAD here we have
three time frames in sync the week is
bullish the daily is bullish and the 4
Hour is bullish so on The Daily time
frame you can see this very clear
inverted Head and Shoulders at this area
of Interest this invert ahead and
shoulders not only has it been completed
but we've broken the neck line and now
we're retesting this area of interest
that it has 1 2 3 4 five six touches and
now what I'm going to be waiting for is
on the lower time frame for price to
then give me my entry signal and my
shifter structure beautiful break and
retest beautiful pullback continuation
now I'm going going to be waiting for
the shift on the lower time frames I'm
going to be waiting for the shift on
this 1 hour I'm going to be Wai for the
break and retest of this Zone in order
to take this trade to the upside it
could be on the 1 hour 30 minute
whichever comes first ideally what I
would want is for this to pretty much
give me a 4H hour bullish engulfing cuz
then that what it would do is is on the
1 hour it would pretty much break that
structure point right there in order for
me to take that trade next we have Euro
JPY which is a very solid trade setup
and you guys can tell how right here
this is a super strong area of Interest
we have 1 2 3 4 five touches I wouldn't
count this one because we have broken
above that zone and then on top of that
we have another Head and Shoulders
another
one where now we have broken the
neckline we are retesting it and this
area of Interest has also a round
psychological level of
57500 so the easiest trade I can do here
is literally wait for the break and
retest under the break and retest under
on the the 1 hour is going to be a very
clear break and retest of this potential
Head and Shoulders as well so I need for
price to pretty much just have this
break have the retest and then I sell
that's going to be retesting one the 1H
hour EMA two area of Interest three
round psychological level four neckline
of The Head and Shoulders on the 1 hour
so many things are going to be happening
if this does this so that's why we're
going to be remaining patient and I have
more pairs for the week but this just
going to be my top three I'm 10 that was
some heat like if you pay attention to
what I just did right there that's some
heat but to show you guys right now it
is currently Sunday 740 at uh night
let's see if we get some trades during
Lon let's go all right what is up guys
so it is Monday morning it's 1034 in the
morning I don't know why my hoodie is
like this so currently took Euro JPY and
a loss right now let me show you guys so
as of right now this is where the
current balance of the account is Euro
JPY we are about um $6,000 in profit
uh well no hold on this is a let me show
you guys Euro JPY so we're going to
explain that trade right now so Euro JPY
you guys can see we're currently in draw
down in the trade exactly what I wanted
to happen on this trade happened we had
a perfect left head right shoulder a
perfect retest of the neckline retest of
the EMA beautiful bearish engulfing on
the 1 hour there's nothing else I can
ask for this trade I took this trade cuz
it's just exactly what I wanted and then
we have our stop loss that is right
above of this zone right here which is a
previous lower high so if price hits
that we're pretty much ultimately wrong
on the overall direction little bit of
draw down right now it's annoying but it
is what it is currently down
$7,000 uh we're just going to hit the
little quick set and figure out on this
trade until we either hit stop loss or
go back into profit
nzd uh JPY didn't break in retest so far
as strong as I wanted to looks like
we're doing that about right now and
then last but not least is AUD CAD which
we are having the break so we're having
the break exactly as I was explaining um
last night I already took off the arrow
that was like this yesterday because
we've already broken so now I'm only
focused on the retest of the pair to
come back and retest this very strong
level of support we haven't body closed
under this in a very long time so now
the fact that we've done it can mean
that there is a high probability of
there being a retest just as there was
here so then we can continue heading to
the downside so once again this is how
we're currently looking on the account
and we'll check back in probably in like
another hour or two let's see where the
trades uh go but for now I don't forget
all right guys so market update it is
currently 8:00 at night so pretty much
nothing uh additional has happened since
the morning other than we got stopped
out of the trade we didn't go as
aggressive as I wanted to because it's
the first trade of the week usually I
like going the first trade of the week
pretty much a little bit less than the
aggressive approach and luckily it
played out in our favor so let me
actually just show you guys all right so
we're currently at 116,000 so we took a
loss on the trade ear earlier this
morning this is pretty much where the
p&l on the account is so obviously the
account was up a very solid amount the
highest it's been up was 131 you guys
can see right here the p&l going up
taking the little dip we've taken a
total of 25 trades and our win rate is a
64% win rate so 16 out of those trades
I've won nine out of those trades I have
lost and you guys can see here that this
trade right here has given us a very
solid reason to stop us out so we've
broken above the structure points from
this point right here we had a bullish
Candle on the daily time frame uh just
getting this fixed there you go so we've
had a daily Candlestick rejection uh a
daily dogey but didn't manage to close
under the daily area of Interest I don't
like how the 4 Hour as well managed to
close above that structure point right
there so these are just all things that
I don't like from this pair that it's
given us so for right now my Buy Still
Remains the Same still going to be
waiting for these break and retests to
then sell in order to continue the trade
to the downside but this is our first
loss for the week next we have nzdcad
which I'm going to be scaling in a
position very soon if it gives us a
little quick pullback we have a
beautiful left head right shoulder we
just have to come in now and kind of
retest that neckline to head to the
upside but everything is happening
perfectly as I'm anticipating uh just
kind of missed the trade I guess I mean
it's still just about four Pips of in
profit I can still enter it here not a
bad idea but obviously just the risk of
reward needs to be worth it so I'm going
to wait for a little quick pull back
into here to enter the trade and then
last but not least it's going to be AUD
CAD which AUD CAD we are going to then
wait for our entry signals rejecting
that strong level of support which is
having the pull back exactly like I'm
anticipating so if you notice this
pullback has now happened now we're
going to be waiting for the rejections
to enter the trade at this level so not
an amazing start to the week but it's
only Monday night there's still plenty
of opportunity and these other
opportunities that are lining up now I
like them equally as good as Euro JPY
and I'm going to be taking a bigger risk
on it cuz you know we got a we got a go
to hit this week so I'll keep you guys
updated later throughout the night uh if
I catch the trade now in London I
usually catch it from my bed I you know
I'm a human I have to sleep and then if
not we'll update during New York so stay
tuned all right good morning guys so it
is the next morning and exactly what I
explained last night on nzd JPY and AUD
JPY has happened and this is a very
valuable lesson to show you guys on
sometimes you're going to have pairs
like your JPY and NCD JPY that they both
have completely different directions and
then they're going to play out in the
same direction but you're going to take
pairs against each other let me explain
what I mean by that so trade up there
this is exactly how we are on the
account right now we're up about $40,000
so we're almost at last week's take
profit we're not even up in this week's
profit where we're supposed to be but
it's okay that's the see plenty of
opportunity in the market as you guys
can see this is exactly what I explained
last night perfect break and retest of
the neckline of this head and shoulders
on the lower time frames this exactly
what we were anticipating retest of the
EMA you have your 30 minute bullish
engulfing Candlestick right there and
then you have the next scale in on the
30 minute time frame which is pretty
much the next higher low once you have
the higher high then you have the next
higher low to then give you this extra
bullish Eng engulfing confirmation this
next structure point that's where I
added and scaled into the next position
and as of right now we've came up all
the way up to the takeprofit point that
I have marked right now which this line
right here if you look all the way to
the left it has been respected multiple
times in the past it has been used as
resistance resistance resistance and
then support so it can potentially be
used as resistance right now so I'm
going to decide what I'm going to do in
the next 5 to 10 minutes to see if I
close it or if I let it run to see if it
has more profits then Euro JPY yesterday
we were looking for the sales and then
this is exactly what I was just
explaining right now both of these pairs
have the JPY meaning one has Euro JPY
and then the other is nzd uh nzd JPY and
the other is Euro JPY so they're
supposed to move in the same direction
CU they have the JPY and that's not the
case really but as you can tell for this
example right here they have but that
doesn't mean that I'm supposed to take a
Buy on this when the sells look good I'm
the type of Trader that I take a trade
on whatever makes the most sense and at
this trade that very moment sells made
the most sense cuz the majority of the
trend were to the downside versus here
taking a buy makes the most sense
because all three time frames are in
that direction so I'm basically just
going to take whatever the market shows
me not what I think and then next we
have AUD CAD which exactly how I
explained as well had the retest of the
area perfectly as I was expecting and as
I was explaining yesterday just didn't
manage to cast this one I was just
focusing on nzd JP why but once again
the set forget strategy has stried on
the market so this is only Tuesday
morning it is currently Tuesday morning
at 8:43 in the morning so looking pretty
good to have a good foundation to
technically start the week cuz we have
just hit last week's takeprofit um I
personally think there can still be
another two three moves on not these
pairs but other pairs throughout the
week to give us those profits that we
need in order to be able to complete
this challenge obviously not in 60 days
now but maybe 90 days so I'll keep you
guys updated on exactly what goes down
and by the way we got the drift car back
today so they're going to SHP us a drift
cart but there's a hurricane in Miami
right now well you can't tell right now
but it pops up whenever it wants so I'll
keep you guys updated all right trade
update so it is currently 9:30 at night
so the trade earlier this morning
obviously we Clos it this morning but I
could have still been holding the trades
and I could have even made more profit
but I didn't want to get greedy I wanted
to have a nice cushion for this Beast of
a trade that we're about to take right
now that I'm pretty much going to go all
into let me show you guys right now this
is where the account is currently
settling at 161,000 right now which is
the balance where I should have been at
the beginning of the week because the
profits that I should have had last week
let me show you guys my analysis for
this week so audcad had already pretty
much retested the area that I wanted to
take the trade and then it hit the
takeprofit Zone but now we're pulling
back up at that zone because I like how
the daily Candlestick has closed as a
daily Wick I think this next daily
Candlestick is going to fill if I go
down to the 1 hour you can see how we're
pretty much about to you know create a
structure Point under this level right
here in the next 25 minutes so that's
where I'm going to decide if it body
closes under I'll take a trade with a
little small 20 pip stop loss and then
I'll probably have a bigger takeprofit
for around here for about 40 Pips and
then if not what I can do is I can wait
for a little quick pullback which I will
get a left head and then a right
shoulder which I'll pretty much have an
entry right here and then I'll probably
add another entry at the retest of the
neckline so a cad is looking very solid
um our nzd JPY trade we pretty much
closed right around this area right here
which was pretty solid right before like
the pullback which we would have been
much more profit if I would have kept
holding but it is what it is now I'm not
going to say I'm done with it but what I
am going to keep expecting is for price
to now come back and pretty much if it
gives me another high low around this
area I would then take the trade again
around here if not I'm going to wait for
a bigger pull back like the daily time
frame which I think it might do it which
is going to have a big pullback into
around this level here before then
pulling up to the upside again so if
that happens then that means that the 4
hours is obviously going to come deeper
so this trade is pretty much gone so if
we don't pull back into around this
level and then reject I think we can
then pull back into around this level
here to then have the push to the upside
so we got that in the pipeline and then
we got AUD CAD which I'm going to be
potentially entering very very soon so
stay tuned hope at you guys tomorrow in
the morning all right good morning guys
so it is Wednesday morning and last
night's trade pretty much exactly as I
explained as well avoided one loss on
AUD Cad and then we got into the nzdjpy
continuations like once you understand
the pair that already has three time
frames in sync and you've already done
the weekly analysis and the weekly is
destined to continue going for the rest
of the week you just keep going with the
trend that is the easiest part like we
already did the hard part with just
finding the pair and understanding the
trend now you just keep going with the
wave like why you want to get out fast
so let me show you all right so this is
where we're currently sitting in profit
about 40K so I literally just took the
same exact trade as yesterday we just
continued going with the trend so as you
guys can see here this is
nzdjpy we took these buys yesterday you
guys already know we explained this
yesterday you guys saw it go down break
retest continuation easy then we said
exactly what we're going to do last
night which is create the higher low we
enter ENT at the first rejection and
then we enter at the next rejection
right at London session and at the same
exact thing left head right shoulder and
look at the
time 3:15 in the morning same exact
thing as pretty much every single night
like do you guys think that we just did
a whole weekly analysis we've understood
that this weekly time frame is pretty
much creating a higher low right now
like it's literally creating a higher
low to create a new higher high this
created a higher low to create a higher
high right now we're about to create
that Weekly higher high why why why
should we just get a little quick 20 30
pip move there's so much upside on this
trade that it is insane we've been
trapped in this consolidation zone for
about 50 days we had a beautiful
breakout a beautiful retest of the
neckline of The Head and Shoulders left
head right shoulder and now all we're
doing is just continuing with the trend
like it's really that easy I see this
pair hitting all the way take profits up
here and now we're just getting into the
trades as the momentum keeps on going so
my first take profit is right here and
I'm just going to keep set and
forgetting because this trade has loads
of upside potential I'm talking about
loads of upside potential so AUD CAD
last night uh didn't give me the entry
signal that I was looking for at this
area so we simply never took the trade
this would pretty much be the second
entry on this trade but it just never
gave us the exact thing entry signal
that we are needing but it is what it is
so now we're just going to keep waiting
for the same exact thing which would be
the break and retest of the Zone once
again so we never took this so we would
just be waiting for something like this
break and then retest to then sell and
this is a prime example and it shows you
guys that trading is not hard like once
you find the right pair once you find
the right momentum once you find the
direction of the market you just keep
going with the wave man like this you
it's not rck science you know so this is
where a lot of Traders able to see the
market keep going and not be able to get
in they get greedy and then they just
kind of go crazy you need to be very
relaxed you need to be very levelheaded
because if not this Market will humble
you
so this is a perfect example of set and
forget perfect example of your trend is
your friend so we're going to continue
to hold the trade now probably for like
the next 30 40 minutes let's see how the
candlesticks close and I'll keep you
guys updated you know what I'm going to
show you guys one thing one thing that I
show all of my students with the head
and shoulders that is my reversal
pattern my not my reversal but my
favorite reversal pattern that has given
me the majority of My Success like what
I'm about to show you guys do not take
it for granted this is taking me forever
to perfect and to actually see it play
out time and time again do not take this
for granted what I'm about to show you
guys The Head and Shoulders reversal
pattern is right here left head and then
right shoulder The Head and Shoulder
shoulders reversal pattern will be a
reversal pattern for a long time
especially on the daily time frame
meaning that this reversal pattern can
have our actual take profit of where we
should close this trade and that is
double the size of the head so if you
were to measure the head you would go
from the body of the head all the way to
the neckline of the head and shoulders
and what you would do is you would copy
and paste that line right there which is
the length of the head and then what you
would do is you would put it right at
that point of where the neckline is and
would you look at that it takes us to
our takeprofit point which is right to
the next structure point and that is not
a coincidence that is because this is
the most valid and the most powerful
reversal pattern there is in the whole
market and if we were to copy and paste
it again you guys can see that we do the
head once again and this goes all the
way up to where right next to the next
structure point which which is the final
take profit our take profits are based
off of structure points you guys can see
how this happens perfectly like you
can't make this up and this is a gem
that I teach my students and this has
been something I keep very private but
I'm going to put it out here for you
guys because you guys have been
following the journey now for pretty
much nine weeks so this structure point
right here not only is it a coincidence
that it's my take profit but it's also
the head of the inverted Head and
Shoulders which is take profit one take
profit two is that structure point right
there so do not let this gem go over
your guys' head trust
me all right market update so it is
currently 10:33 so about an hour since
the last time we updated it we're up
about 53,000 right now so look ins
started we're at our first take profit
point so based off of that point right
there we're going to see how we end up
closing this trade but pretty much at
the highest point we have been so
far all right so trade update uh it's
currently 3:00 so the last time that I
ate was 9:00 yesterday so that's I'm
about like a 17 17 and 1 half 18 hour
fast so that's probably the secret on
how I've lost so much weight and
honestly I feel good like it sixs at the
beginning obviously you get hungry and
stuff it sucks but it is what it is so
this is currently trade up there right
now on the account so we're up about
212,000 uh we closed a trade earlier
when I mentioned that it was pretty much
hit our takeprofit to the te and would
you look at that L what I was explaining
about the take profit being double The
Head and Shoulders look how perfect that
works for the te and on top of that Not
only was it the head of the head and
shoulders but it was also that structure
point right there so like you guys can
see how the set and forget strategy
shows you to the T not only how to have
the strategy to enter the trade but how
to close it at the right point so right
now we're going to go eat something
all so look hack let me show you hack so
that left light is going to turn left
right now it's going to take forever so
we're going to take this red light that
we just happen to take right now we're
going to pop the U-turn we don't wait
the red light feel me oh
[__] so look that would have been us
over there look TR that would have been
us over there but we just finessed the
system just like that know what
I'm
well I haven't figured out how to
finesse traffic yet but I'll get back to
you guys when we get to that the point
is that c AIG it works I'm going to not
try and force more trades for the week
because you know my goal for the week is
300K so I can get one more trade and I
don't think you guys realize how close I
am to actually completing this already
cuz if you think about it when I turned
1,000 to 3K wasn't a big deal but I
flipped the account by two times if I do
the same flip right now it means I'm
going to turn 200 into 600 ,000 and
that's it I just got to flip it one more
time and I'm at to MK like people think
just because it's a bigger numbers that
it's crazier it's the same exact thing
it's the same trades everything is
exactly the same just some people
they've never had big numbers they've
never had you know six figures floating
up and down so then they don't really
comprehend it or understand it and they
think it's crazy trust me it's the same
[__] it's just numbers on the screen all
right so we just f up the saacks to shop
get some clothes got some jeans Mall
pants pants you we the mall as a sign of
respect came to show you but I'm
Barefoot if there one pet peeve I have
is I can't walk Barefoot I [__] hate
that [__] so it's how we walking right
now they good though right yeah they're
fire fire I'm taking these jeans but I
don't want to take them off so we got
the tag on it I was I was about I was
about to run off but she caught me so
now I got to put my leg up here to take
it
off close
and you thought I was going to do that
all by myself you're
crazy you thought I was going to do the
AL myself
okay all right we're good [__] [__] out
yo I just figured out how to turn on
drift mode all right little less drift n
you know what all the way drift oh B we
about to hit it right
now and if we hold this button all the
way down
d off confirmation confirm selection
confirm why canceled
why okay look confirm selection yes turn
off
traction cancel [__] bro actually it
does turn off so we're going to turn
traction back on where is
it turn back on thank you that was close
that was
close cuz we're going too fast
[Music]
that's a traction
onuh maybe doesn't do it in
first maybe do much in
first we're figuring it out as this
goes all right guys so market update and
I just pretty much came back to the
market trying out been out all day and
actual chills that I have right now for
how I predicted this market and how
we've been predicting this Market time
and time again the set and forget
strategy like like I I don't know if you
guys can see the actual chills right now
but let me just show you guys so you
guys can see this is AUD CAD that I've
been calling from the beginning of the
week and I explained to you guys I would
look to enter if it broke and then
retested that to then sell look at that
beautiful break little Wick retest to
then sell this is on the 4 hour time
frame if I go down to the 1 hour time
frame you guys can see how it has that
perfect retest of the neckline of the
area of Interest left head right
shoulder EMA bearish and golf everything
and it's not even that you guys look at
here in the free telegram I literally
sent this at 2:24 in the afternoon I
said the first one didn't play out
didn't retest there perfectly so let's
wait for the next break and retest and
look at this not even 12 hours later
look at the update right now set forget
strategy for the win once again
88,000 members have seen this absolutely
insane nzd JPY trade has pulled back we
pulled out perfectly at the takeprofit
level due to the fact that it was this
structure point and due to the fact that
it was double the head of the inverted
Head and Shoulders like look how precise
this gets time and time again so I'm
going to be looking to add a position
now uh once and if we break this
15minute lower high structure so I need
the 15minute time frame to come here and
then basically break and then retest
this area to then head to the upside I'm
going to be waiting for that in order to
take this trade because it's where it
would make the most sense because right
now we've had a very strong daily Wick
pullback back but can help to notice
that we are retesting this pretty okay
for our area of Interest so last but not
least is going to be Euro JPY which
we're going to to still be waiting for
the same exact thing same exact break
and retest to then sell to the downside
um because earlier this week we got
stopped out on it so looking solid so
far it is currently Thursday
12:28 a.m. so we're about to enter
London session very very soon and it's
crazy like I'm out here putting these
hours day and day out I don't know if
you guys can see but like my eyes are
like purple like I barely sleep just for
this challenge to get it out the way as
soon as I complete this challenge I'm
going to take a week or two off
completely from the markets I haven't
left my house in two months you guys
know I love traveling to places and I
haven't been able to just cuz I want to
have the laser focus for this challenge
but I'm doing this for you guys I'm
doing this to show you guys that it's
possible all you just need is the right
strategy to do it and some proper risk
management along with patience anything
can get done all right market update so
it is currently Thursday 700 p.m. EST
the account right now is exactly the
same we haven't taken any trades just to
show you guys 12 what is it
2 12,000
so I don't want to say I'm done trading
for the week but I don't see any A+
setups in the market right and I want
you guys to understand how close I am to
completing this challenge we are
literally almost there all I have to do
is flip it I think four or five more
times it was harder for me to turn $100
into 1,000 than it is for me turning
200k into a mill now it's just a
percentage game not a numbers game keep
that in mind so let me show you guys
kind of where the market is right now
I'm not really like a big fan of it so
right now nzdjpy as I explained this
morning it has rejected perfectly this
strong level of resistance we've had a
very strong daily bearish engulfing
pulling back to this area once again
pretty much where we started off the
week and then after we started off the
week we had the push off the retest
going up and now we're at this area
again so we might do the same thing that
we did before again which is literally
break and retest the zone so what I mean
by that is we're obviously down here in
the zone so we might just break and then
retest and do it again so we might just
have that same exact play happen right
here break then retest and then do it
again if that happens then I will
potentially take the trade because we
have a left head and then this will kind
of be like the right shoulder we'll be
retesting the neck line of The Head and
Shoulder retest in the EMA retesting the
area of interest just the same thing
once again next we have we have Euro JPY
which we got stopped out earlier this
week right here we got stopped out price
kept going up to the upside for a little
bit and now we're back under the Zone
pretty much doing exactly what I had
anticipated very strong and bearish
marabu daily Candlestick am Mar bozza
when there is no Wick at the top or the
bottom of a Candlestick showing very
strong bearish indication or if it's to
the upside bullish indication for
example this is another bearish marabu
if you can see every single time there's
one of those there's huge momentum after
that you can see here once again huge
bearish marabu and then huge bearish
momentum to the downside so we could
potentially have that once again right
here if you notice this right here huge
bearish marabu but then we rejected cuz
we were Above This resistance level in
this case we're actually under it so I
can potentially wait for now a little
quick pullback and then to sell not
super excited about it but I'm just
keeping it in mind so I'm going to wait
for some rejections around here to then
take this trade to the downside next we
have AUD CAD which had the break and
retest perfectly as I expected and I'd
say it's pretty much gone there's
nothing we can do about it now uh the
trade that we were looking to take it
happened and now we just have to sit on
the sidelines until another one happens
so this trade happened perfectly to the
set and forget T so now it's gone we
can't chase it we just move on to the
next one and that's what a lot of
Traders aren't willing to do all of
these pairs are for me not that
interested except Euro AUD asz we're
coming back to retesting this area of
Interest daily EMA Brown psychological
level 166 500 but I don't like how the 4
Hour kind of is looking right around
this level so I don't know going to keep
my eye on it uh for now just going to
look at Euro JPY and potentially Euro
AUD for sales if I get what I'm looking
for at this area of Interest
so sad don't forget our goal is 300K for
the week let's see if we can squeeze
something tonight for London for the
last London session of the week if not
we'll come back next week and just do it
again once again all right what is up
guys good morning so officially the
trade that we caught last night has
given us 100K floating and profit right
now it was probably up like 990,000
couple minutes ago and I just finished
the Instagram stories right now which I
can literally show you guys right now
the these things are hilarious look at
this did come on stop [__] around
come on come on almost there come on
come on L there we go boys officially
100K let's go let's go let's go
100K
100K 100 I got hyped I got hyped for
Instagram but officially we've hit 100K
on the account so let me show you guys
exactly what I explained last night
happened to Perfection so this is
currently where we are sitting on the
account we are currently of about
$101,000 floating in profit and this is
on the Euro AUD trick trade that we
explained yesterday to Perfection
literally the exact same Zone that I
drew out yesterday the same exact spot I
basically expected the break expected
the retest of the zone to then sell that
is exactly what we have gotten right now
so now that we've got in this break and
retest I entered the first entry signal
literally at that bearish engulfing
Candlestick right around here which was
our evening star formation and then I
entered on the next one after this huge
bearish candle I entered right on the
top of that pullback right there so it
was a pretty nice pullback well not all
the way in the top it was pretty much
like halfway at the top until it was
retesting the zone right here so this
was our second entry on this trade so
this is absolutely to Perfection once
again the set and figet strategy doing
its thing now we're floating about
$98,000 in profit so going to wait for
this to uh probably the next 5 to 8
minutes cuz then I just want to close
right now don't need any more profits to
close off the week we hit our goal and
then last but not least Euro I mean
nzdjpy exactly what I explained last
night has just happened which is the
breakout of this structure point right
here so I explain as soon as we break
above this structure point I'll be
waiting for then the retest to then go
along we broke out never got the retest
and look at this this like went through
the screen so this shows you guys once
again the set fig strategy doing the
finest moves it's just absolutely
absolutely insane that I I don't even
know how to explain like throughout this
challenge I realized how good of a
Trader I am so I'm going to wait
probably another couple of minutes to
see how this closes probably see if we
can fill that bearish candle to the down
side to see if we can probably get a
little bit more profit um but other than
that I will keep you guys updated all
right so we officially closed the trade
but I want to show you guys what I get
retagged every single day on Instagram
cuz I feel like I never show it here on
YouTube of everybody catching these
trades of me calling it live on my
Instagram let me show you guys as you
guys can see this is my Instagram and
literally everybody catches a trade for
example this guy was is up $5,000 off
the trade this guy caught it off the
story as well this next Trader here
caught it from the set and forget you
guys can see here I get constant DMS of
people thanking me for these type of
Trades like I can also go
here or I can also go here to like the
stories and just people tag me all the
time that they're catching these trades
look that is the Euro AUD trade
literally everybody catches the trades
that I sent and I get tagged on it
constantly look at it there once again
Euro AUD and it just keeps going Euro
AUD once again go trade Euro they caught
the move everything just off of the
Instagram story we officially closed the
trade at this area let's go so I just
saw a DM right now and the guy was like
hey bro like what did you do different
now to make that 100K Prof profit on
this trade compared to the other ones
and I literally said nothing I haven't
done anything different everything is
exactly the same the only thing that is
different is the account size and what
I'm risking that is simple but you guys
get blinded by the money you guys get
blinded by 100K in profit and that's
what you guys care about you guys don't
care about what had to get put behind
that 100K in order to make that money I
am taking the same exact trades that I
took at the beginning of the challenge
that I took last week that I took four
months ago that I took a year ago that I
took two years ago that I've been taking
my whole entire Journey since I've been
profitable nothing has changed it is the
exact same trade now just because I made
100K that means that the trade is
different or there's a specific strategy
no it's the same thing the only thing
that changes is the risk management and
the account size the moment you guys
understand that you will be profitable
because you can do anything you want
once you have the profitable strategy if
you have a profitable strategy you can
apply it and you will succeed it is
simple so I want to make I want to make
that very clear this is the same exact
strategy don't think just because it's a
bigger number something has changed the
only thing that has changed is the lot
size and what I'm about to do with the
challenge on I'm done with it you guys
can see everything right here to
Perfection we are up
$39,000 this looks literally insane in
the p&l chart so so far for this week we
have a total of about, 400% for the
month we have about
135% for the week percentage wise so
obviously when you look at it this
percentage wise and maybe like this it
might look like a lot but when you look
at it like this on a daytoday on a week
toe basis it's not much regarding the
high risk I don't think $100 took me to
300K not at all this is the percentage
that I made for the week because if I
did not turn $100 into 300K I turned
200k into 300K so that's the percentage
that I got so total so far we have 31
trades that we have taken with with a
70% win rate 30% loss rate so so far the
SF strategy is
7030 looking very very good all right so
let's have a recap of how the week went
this week started off with a loss we had
a first loss of the week which probably
put us down about $10,000 from what I
remember right now but then later that
night I explained to you guys the next
opportunity that we had on nzdjpy and
AUD C nzdjpy is a prime example of a
continuation Trend literally we just
continue buying with the weekly continue
buying with the daily continue buying
with the 4our inverter Head and
Shoulders break and ret like that is all
you need to succeed we bought it we
scaled in and then we hit our takeprofit
and we scaled in once again which gave
us great profits on the trade and put us
up a lot of profits and then next we had
AUD CAD which then we missed the trade
played out perfectly as we anticipated
and that trade was something that I
would take time and time again but
obviously all of my efforts were put on
NTV JPY at the time but it shows you how
out of three solid trade setups I was
anticipating at the beginning of the
week two of them played out very well
that is why every single time I go on
Sunday Swings with the students and I
analyze the pairs of the week I always
do anywhere from three to four to five
top pairs for the week that we look to
trade on the week ahead now we didn't
look to trade all of them we just look
to trade the ones that have the best
probability setups this is a very prime
example of a very solid week and how the
center PR strategy Works once again if
you want to know more about the set PR
strategy and how my students are making
anywhere from 1,000 to $1,500 a week
using my set and forget strategy hit the
link in the description below I have a
video that explains what the set and
forget strategy actually consist about
there's a lot of different theories
about it and what it actually means and
the video below is going to explain to
it because you guys are seeing week time
and time again how I'm predicting these
markets there's a very simple
explanation that has taken me about 5
and 1 half years almost 6 years now to
complete it in a way where it's very
easy for you to understand and you make
anywhere from $1,000 to $1,500 a week as
it begin ctif foret Traer so appreci
appreciate you guys watching this video
all the way to the end if you learned
anything drop a comment and make sure
you guys watch these videos again
because there's so much value in these
videos that I wish I had when I started
trading and I'm sure you guys are not
only learning but you guys are
completely changing your lives and the
legacy of your family forever so
appreciate you guys watching this video
to the end I'll see you guys in the next
one